[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which cast member of the TV drama Dallas starred in the film Earthquake?", "correct_answer": "Victoria Principal", "incorrect_answers": ["Larry Hagman", "Patrick Duffy", "Mary Crosby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the correct name of an African nation?", "correct_answer": "Republic of South Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Republic of North Africa", "Federation of South Africa", "Federation of North Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nose pad of a cat is unique like the human fingerprint.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of John Candys characters wife in the movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles?", "correct_answer": "Marie", "incorrect_answers": ["Lauren", "Kathleen", "Mary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is an adult male rooster known as?", "correct_answer": "Rooster", "incorrect_answers": ["Buck", "Hen", "Foul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is commonly used to refer to the guinea pig?", "correct_answer": "Cavy", "incorrect_answers": ["Netty", "Poppy", "Willy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national flag of what country consists of a light blue field with a single white star in the center?", "correct_answer": "Somalia", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Sudan", "Singapore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sizes are for those 5 4 - 5 5 tall, who have a higher bust and a shorter back?", "correct_answer": "Junior", "incorrect_answers": ["Miss Petite", "Junior Petite", "Young Junior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish this Irish saying: A tune is more lasting than the song of birds. And a word is more lasting than ________.", "correct_answer": "the wealth of the world", "incorrect_answers": ["an old mans teeth", "a maidens beauty", "a bottle of whiskey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term Honeymoon originates from the times when a man and a woman remained in hiding for certain cycles of the moon and did this.", "correct_answer": "Drank honey wine", "incorrect_answers": ["Ate honeydew melons", "Chased honey bees", "Ate honey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the gestation period for a female tiger shark?", "correct_answer": "15-16 months", "incorrect_answers": ["20-21 months", "10-12 weeks", "9-10 Months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which group consists of these three members: Thomas (Tom) Matthew DeLonge on guitar, Markus (Mark) Allan Hoppus on bass, and Travis Landon Barker on drums?", "correct_answer": "Blink-182", "incorrect_answers": ["East 17", "Take That", "Wax"]}]